<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<fmg>
<filename>アイテムうんちく.fmg</filename>
<compression>None</compression>
<version>DarkSouls3</version>
<bigendian>False</bigendian>
<entries>
<text id="100">Dangling, upside-down rune etched in one's mind.
Symbol of a hunter.

By focusing one's thoughts on this rune, a hunter
loses all Blood Echoes, but awakens afresh,
as if it were all just a bad dream.</text>
<text id="111">Hunters are linked by the resonance of bells
with special encoded timbres. This inaudible
burst disrupts such resonance.

Fire to end cooperation, and prevent further
cooperation. Firing this does not disrupt the
resonance of a Sinister Bell.</text>
<text id="112">%null%</text>
<text id="113">%null%</text>
<text id="114">%null%</text>
<text id="115">%null%</text>
<text id="116">%null%</text>
<text id="117">%null%</text>
<text id="118">%null%</text>
<text id="119">%null%</text>
<text id="120">Messengers are inhabitants of the dream who revere the brave hunters. Use them to send messages to other worlds.

Leave notes with messengers, read the notes left to messengers in other worlds, and rate notes to reach out to hunters across planes of existence.

Note: Online use only. Cannot use this item offline.</text>
<text id="121">%null%</text>
<text id="122">%null%</text>
<text id="123">%null%</text>
<text id="124">%null%</text>
<text id="125">%null%</text>
<text id="126">%null%</text>
<text id="127">%null%</text>
<text id="128">%null%</text>
<text id="129">%null%</text>
<text id="130">Red-leather record of the Vilebloods loyal to the covenant of Annalise, Queen of the Vilebloods, at Cainhurst Castle.

A record of the Vilebloods, blood-lusting hunters who seek blood dregs of their prey, kept throughout the ages.

Note: Online use only. Cannot use this item offline.</text>
<text id="131">The League staff is the sign of a confederate.
A directory within the hilt lists the names of fellow confederates.

Members of the League brandish this staff to indicate themselves to fellow members of the League.

There shall be no sympathy for those engaged in the bloody mission of the League. No matter that an oath must be taken to uphold the illusion.</text>
<text id="200">Great old bell discovered in the underground labyrinth.

Its ring resonates across worlds, and the first hunter used it as a special signal to call hunters from other worlds to cross the gap and cooperate.

A human must use Insight to ring this uncanny bell, but the benefits of cross-world cooperation are many.</text>
<text id="201">%null%</text>
<text id="202">%null%</text>
<text id="203">%null%</text>
<text id="204">%null%</text>
<text id="205">Small bell discovered in the old underground labyrinth.

Its ring resonates across worlds, and the first hunter
used it as a special signal to call hunters from other
worlds to cross the gap and cooperate.

This bell resonates with its counterpart, the Beckoning
Bell. Ring to help hunters in other worlds.

Note: Online use only. Cannot use this item offline.</text>
<text id="225">A blood-stained bell discovered in the old underground labyrinth.

One of the resonating bells that cross the gaps of worlds, but this one knells for misfortune and malice.

The Sinister Bell is an object of dark thoughts. Ring it to become the enemy of a hunter in another world.

Note: Online use only. Cannot use this item offline.</text>
<text id="700">A small music box received from a young Yharnam girl.
Plays a song shared by her mother and father.

Inside the lid is a small scrap of paper, perhaps an
old message. Two names can be made out, however faintly.

Viola and Gascoigne.</text>
<text id="701">Blood taken from Arianna, Cathedral Ward woman of
pleasure. The sweet blood of Arianna restores HP,
and temporarily speeds stamina recovery.

A member of the old Healing Church would know
that her blood is similar indeed, to precisely what
was once forbidden.</text>
<text id="702">Blood taken from Adella, nun of the Healing Church.
Restores an amount of HP, then continues to gradually
restore HP for a short time.

The Healing Church nuns are chosen for their merit
as vessels for blood, and groomed as Blood Saints.
The mere chance of being treated with their blood
lends legitimacy to the Healing Church and communion.</text>
<text id="703">Blood vial acquired from Iosefka's clinic.

This refined blood, highly invigorating,
restores a larger amount of HP.

The product of a slow and careful refinement process,
this rare blood vial appears to be a clinic original.</text>
<text id="704">The Vilebloods of Cainhurst, blood-lusting hunters,
see these frightful things in coldblood.

They often appear in the blood of echo fiends, that is to say, the blood of hunters. Queen Annalise partakes in these blood dregs offerings, so that she may one day bear the Child of Blood, the next Vileblood heir.</text>
<text id="705">Blood received from Annalise, Vileblood Queen of Cainhurst.

Vileblood hunters who offer sufficient blood dregs are allowed the special honor of imbibing this blood.

The sensually sweet gelatinous blood restores HP and temporarily speeds stamina recovery.</text>
<text id="706">Blood taken from Adeline, patient of the research hall. Restores HP, then continues to rejuvenate HP for some time.

Adeline was originally one of the Blood Saints who received treatment by the Church to cultivate worthy blood. Adeline's was one of the few cases that turned out favorably.</text>
<text id="900">Special bullets used with hunter firearms.

Ordinary bullets have no effect on beasts,
and so Quicksilver Bullets, fused with the wielder's
own blood, must be employed.

The strength of Quicksilver Bullets depends greatly
upon the wielder's bloodtinge.</text>
<text id="901">Special equivalents to Quicksilver Bullets.

When a hunter runs out of Quicksilver Bullets,
it is possible to create bullets purely from blood.

Beware of overuse, as their creation greatly drains HP.</text>
<text id="999">*</text>
<text id="1000">Special blood used in ministration. Restores HP.

Once a patient has had their blood ministered, a unique but common treatment in Yharnam, successive infusions recall the first, and are all the more invigorating for it.

No surprise that most Yharnamites are heavy users of blood.</text>
<text id="1100">Small medicinal tablets that counteract poison.

Used to treat ashen blood, the baffling sickness
that ravaged Old Yharnam long ago.

These tablets only provide short-term relief.
The ashen blood ailment eventually triggered
the spread of the beastly scourge.</text>
<text id="1101">Liquid medicine concocted at Byrgenwerth.
Calms the nerves.

Those who delve into the arcane fall all-too-easily
to madness, and thick human blood serves to calm
the frayed nerves of these inquisitive minds. Naturally,
this often leads to a reliance on blood ministration.</text>
<text id="1102">%null%</text>
<text id="1103">%null%</text>
<text id="1104">%null%</text>
<text id="1105">%null%</text>
<text id="1106">%null%</text>
<text id="1107">%null%</text>
<text id="1108">%null%</text>
<text id="1109">%null%</text>
<text id="1110">Large medicinal pellets, supposedly formed of coagulated
beast blood. Banned by the Healing Church due to
their unclear origin. Grants a spurt of beasthood.

Ripping apart the flesh of one's enemies and being
rained upon by their splattering blood invigorates
one's sense of beasthood, feeding strength and
euphoric feeling alike.</text>
<text id="1111">%null%</text>
<text id="1112">%null%</text>
<text id="1113">%null%</text>
<text id="1114">%null%</text>
<text id="1115">%null%</text>
<text id="1116">%null%</text>
<text id="1117">%null%</text>
<text id="1118">%null%</text>
<text id="1119">%null%</text>
<text id="1120">Dubious liquid medicine used in strange experiments
conducted by high ministers of the Healing Church.
A type of anesthetic that numbs the brain.

Hunters, able to retain consciousness by force
of will, make use of a secondary effect of the medicine,
which dilutes their presence while standing still.</text>
<text id="1121">%null%</text>
<text id="1122">%null%</text>
<text id="1123">%null%</text>
<text id="1124">%null%</text>
<text id="1125">%null%</text>
<text id="1126">%null%</text>
<text id="1127">%null%</text>
<text id="1128">%null%</text>
<text id="1129">%null%</text>
<text id="1130">%null%</text>
<text id="1200">Explodes in raging flames when thrown against an object.
One of the oldest hunter tools available in the workshop.

Since the tragedy that struck Old Yharnam, fire has become a staple in beast hunts, and is thought to cleanse impurity.

Certain types of beasts have an abnormal fear of flame.</text>
<text id="1201">A special hunter tool crafted by the old Oto Workshop.
These molotovs wedge into the ground when thrown, and explode on a timed delay.

A shame that such a complex gadget must be sacrificed with each use of this inefficient hunter tool. Nevertheless, delayed molotovs are cherished by the minority of hunters who prefer the tricksier kill. This creation is one of the earliest-known roots of the Powder Kegs.</text>
<text id="1202">%null%</text>
<text id="1203">%null%</text>
<text id="1204">%null%</text>
<text id="1205">%null%</text>
<text id="1206">%null%</text>
<text id="1207">%null%</text>
<text id="1208">%null%</text>
<text id="1209">%null%</text>
<text id="1210">A knife slathered in poison.

This curved knife is as thin and sharp as a surgeon's blade.
Often used for self-defense by special doctors in the Healing Church.

They say that hunters traditionally avoid the use of poison, likely because the poison is too slow to act in the heat of the hunt.</text>
<text id="1211">%null%</text>
<text id="1212">%null%</text>
<text id="1213">%null%</text>
<text id="1214">%null%</text>
<text id="1215">%null%</text>
<text id="1216">%null%</text>
<text id="1217">%null%</text>
<text id="1218">%null%</text>
<text id="1219">%null%</text>
<text id="1220">When this urn hits its mark, the target is drenched
in oil, and made extremely flammable.

Fire is commonplace on the hunt, and oil urns accentuate
its effect. Sometimes, when hunters burn beasts,
they appear intoxicated by the euphoria of purification.</text>
<text id="1221">%null%</text>
<text id="1222">%null%</text>
<text id="1223">%null%</text>
<text id="1224">%null%</text>
<text id="1225">%null%</text>
<text id="1226">%null%</text>
<text id="1227">%null%</text>
<text id="1228">%null%</text>
<text id="1229">%null%</text>
<text id="1230">Small pebbles found throughout Yharnam.

Can be thrown at foes.

Quite thrilling.</text>
<text id="1231">%null%</text>
<text id="1232">%null%</text>
<text id="1233">%null%</text>
<text id="1234">%null%</text>
<text id="1235">%null%</text>
<text id="1236">%null%</text>
<text id="1237">%null%</text>
<text id="1238">%null%</text>
<text id="1239">%null%</text>
<text id="1240">Throwing knife with a finely serrated blade.
One of the old hunter Henryk's favorite weapons.

Does not cause a great deal of damage to beasts,
but with deft use, can distract attackers and
keep them at bay.</text>
<text id="1241">%null%</text>
<text id="1242">%null%</text>
<text id="1243">%null%</text>
<text id="1244">%null%</text>
<text id="1245">%null%</text>
<text id="1246">%null%</text>
<text id="1247">%null%</text>
<text id="1248">%null%</text>
<text id="1249">%null%</text>
<text id="1250">Exploding Molotov cocktail that is thrown behind.

Allows for more maneuvering compared to an ordinary Molotov cocktail, and can catch foes off guard.

Since the tragedy that struck Old Yharnam, fire has become a staple in beast hunts, and is thought to cleanse impurity.

Certain types of beasts have an abnormal fear of flame.</text>
<text id="1251">A special hunter tool crafted by the old Oto Workshop.
These molotovs wedge into the ground when thrown behind one's back, and explode on a timed delay.

A shame that such a complex gadget must be sacrificed with each use of this inefficient hunter tool. Nevertheless, delayed molotovs are cherished by the minority of hunters who prefer the tricksier kill. This creation is one of the earliest-known roots of the Powder Kegs.</text>
<text id="1252">%null%</text>
<text id="1253">%null%</text>
<text id="1254">%null%</text>
<text id="1255">%null%</text>
<text id="1256">%null%</text>
<text id="1257">%null%</text>
<text id="1258">%null%</text>
<text id="1259">%null%</text>
<text id="1260">Mature blood cocktail that releases a pungent odor when
thrown that attracts blood-thirsty beasts.

A precious tool in sadly short supply.
In Yharnam, they produce more blood than alcohol,
as the former is the more intoxicating.</text>
<text id="1261">%null%</text>
<text id="1262">%null%</text>
<text id="1263">%null%</text>
<text id="1264">%null%</text>
<text id="1265">%null%</text>
<text id="1266">%null%</text>
<text id="1267">%null%</text>
<text id="1268">%null%</text>
<text id="1269">%null%</text>
<text id="1270">Throw to create a mist cloud that numbs a hunter's
life essence and prevents restoration of HP.

Said to be used by the blood hunters of Cainhurst,
its recipe is a secret closely guarded by the line of
nobles inhabiting the castle.</text>
<text id="1300">Coarse paper that applies fire to weapons when rubbed.

A hunter tool found in the Healing Church workshop.

Since the tragedy that struck Old Yharnam, fire has become a staple in beast hunts, and is thought to cleanse impurity.

Certain types of beasts have an abnormal fear of flame.</text>
<text id="1301">%null%</text>
<text id="1302">%null%</text>
<text id="1303">%null%</text>
<text id="1304">%null%</text>
<text id="1305">%null%</text>
<text id="1306">%null%</text>
<text id="1307">%null%</text>
<text id="1308">%null%</text>
<text id="1309">%null%</text>
<text id="1310">Empty invertebrate shell that is said to be a familiar of a Great One. The Healing Church has discovered a great variety of invertebrates, or phantasms, as they are called.

Shells with slime still harbor arcane power, and can be rubbed on weapons to imbue them with their strength.</text>
<text id="1311">%null%</text>
<text id="1312">%null%</text>
<text id="1313">%null%</text>
<text id="1314">%null%</text>
<text id="1315">%null%</text>
<text id="1316">%null%</text>
<text id="1317">%null%</text>
<text id="1318">%null%</text>
<text id="1319">%null%</text>
<text id="1320">Coarse paper that applies bolt to weapons when rubbed.

Invented by Archibald, the infamous eccentric of the
Healing Church workshop. Artificially recreates the
blue sparks that are said to surround darkbeasts.

Unlike the other strange weapons created by Archibald,
this one was favored by many hunters, in particular
those who had even once laid eyes on a darkbeast.</text>
<text id="1321">%null%</text>
<text id="1322">%null%</text>
<text id="1323">%null%</text>
<text id="1324">%null%</text>
<text id="1325">%null%</text>
<text id="1326">%null%</text>
<text id="1327">%null%</text>
<text id="1328">%null%</text>
<text id="1329">%null%</text>
<text id="1330">Additional medium that strengthens Quicksilver Bullets.

According to the workshop, this is a special bone marrow ash collected from Hemwick Charnel Lane.

Invaluable to hunters with weak bloodtinge who require the use of stronger firearms.</text>
<text id="1400">Dangling, upside-down rune etched in the mind of a hunter.

The image upon this parchment allows one to envision the rune with clarity.

Allows a hunter to awaken again without losing Blood Echoes, a trick that seems nearly too good to be true.</text>
<text id="1401">%null%</text>
<text id="1402">%null%</text>
<text id="1403">%null%</text>
<text id="1404">%null%</text>
<text id="1405">%null%</text>
<text id="1406">%null%</text>
<text id="1407">%null%</text>
<text id="1408">%null%</text>
<text id="1409">%null%</text>
<text id="1410">Various coins that are particularly luminous.

There are very few uses for spare change during the hunt,
but these will serve as guides through the darkness.

Or, one could save them until morning, if it ever comes.</text>
<text id="1411">Monocular used to view things up close.

Not a hunter's tool, but a simple antique,
to be used as one sees fit.</text>
<text id="1412">Small portable lantern.

This hunting accessory provides light while leaving both hands free to hold weapons.

The torch, however, provides a stronger source of light.</text>
<text id="1500">Skull of a madman touched by the wisdom of the Great Ones.

Use to gain Insight.

Making contact with eldritch wisdom is a blessing, for even if it drives one mad, it allows one to serve a grander purpose, for posterity.</text>
<text id="1501">Fragments of the lost wisdom of the Great Ones,
beings that might be described as gods.

Use to gain Insight.

At Byrgenwerth, Master Willem had an epiphany:
"We are thinking on the basest of planes.
What we need, are more eyes."</text>
<text id="1502">%null%</text>
<text id="1503">%null%</text>
<text id="1504">%null%</text>
<text id="1505">%null%</text>
<text id="1506">%null%</text>
<text id="1507">%null%</text>
<text id="1508">%null%</text>
<text id="1509">%null%</text>
<text id="1510">Droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain Blood Echoes.

Hunters sustained by the dream gain strength from
Blood Echoes. They imbibe the blood with thoughts
of reverence, indeed gratitude, for their victims.</text>
<text id="1511">Droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain Blood Echoes.

Hunters sustained by the dream gain strength from
Blood Echoes. They imbibe the blood with thoughts
of reverence, indeed gratitude, for their victims.</text>
<text id="1512">Droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain Blood Echoes.

Hunters sustained by the dream gain strength from
Blood Echoes. They imbibe the blood with thoughts
of reverence, indeed gratitude, for their victims.</text>
<text id="1513">A thick droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain a larger amount of Blood Echoes.

A strong will produces thick blood. Doubtless,
the product of obsession, a potent source
of human strength.</text>
<text id="1514">A thick droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain a larger amount of Blood Echoes.

A strong will produces thick blood. Doubtless,
the product of obsession, a potent source
of human strength.</text>
<text id="1515">A thick droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain a larger amount of Blood Echoes.

A strong will produces thick blood. Doubtless,
the product of obsession, a potent source
of human strength.</text>
<text id="1516">A rich droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain frenzied Blood Echoes.

This manifestation of madness comes from a mind
teetering on the very brink, but has a sane mind ever
produced anything of true significance?</text>
<text id="1517">A rich droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain frenzied Blood Echoes.

This manifestation of madness comes from a mind
teetering on the very brink, but has a sane mind ever
produced anything of true significance?</text>
<text id="1518">A rich droplet of coldblood containing Blood Echoes.

Use to gain frenzied Blood Echoes.

This manifestation of madness comes from a mind
teetering on the very brink, but has a sane mind ever
produced anything of true significance?</text>
<text id="1519">Coldblood of inhuman kin of the cosmos,
brethren of the Great Ones.

Use to gain unspeakable Blood Echoes.

Dare not to delve into the world beyond humanity,
the eldritch Truth touched upon long ago at Byrgenwerth.</text>
<text id="1590">Coldblood of inhuman kin of the cosmos,
brethren of the Great Ones.

Use to gain unspeakable Blood Echoes.

Dare not to delve into the world beyond humanity,
the eldritch Truth touched upon long ago at Byrgenwerth.</text>
<text id="1591">Coldblood of inhuman kin of the cosmos,
brethren of the Great Ones.

Use to gain unspeakable Blood Echoes.

Dare not to delve into the world beyond humanity,
the eldritch Truth touched upon long ago at Byrgenwerth.</text>
<text id="1592">Relic containing the Blood Echoes of a Great One.

Use to gain cosmically nightmarish Blood Echoes.

Like a true revelation, this uncanny relic defies
understanding. </text>
<text id="1593">Relic containing the Blood Echoes of an old Great One.

Use to gain cosmically nightmarish Blood Echoes.

Like a true revelation, this uncanny relic defies
understanding. </text>
<text id="1594">Relic containing the Blood Echoes of a revered Great One.

Use to gain cosmically nightmarish Blood Echoes.

Like a true revelation, this uncanny relic defies
understanding. </text>
<text id="1595">%null%</text>
<text id="1596">%null%</text>
<text id="1597">%null%</text>
<text id="1598">%null%</text>
<text id="1599">%null%</text>
<text id="1600">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Метаморфоза" збільшує запас ОЗ.</text>
<text id="1601">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Зворотня Метаморфоза" збільшує запас витривалості.</text>
<text id="1602">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Причастя" збільшує кількість ампул з кров'ю.</text>
<text id="1603">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Зв'язок з Одоном" збільшує максимальний запас ртутних куль.</text>
<text id="1604">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Озеро" підвищує захист.</text>
<text id="1605">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Глибоке море" підвищує стійкість.</text>
<text id="1606">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Руйнівник" посилює смертельні атаки.</text>
<text id="1607">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Гедоніст" відновлює ОЗ від ураження внутрішніх органів.</text>
<text id="1608">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Зв'язок" відновлює ртутні кулі від ураження внутрішніх
органів.</text>
<text id="1609">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна  "Спадщина" дає більше кровавих спогадів від ураження
внутрішніх органів.</text>
<text id="1610">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Почвара" підсилює ефект тимчасового перетворення.</text>
<text id="1611">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Місяць" збільшує кількість отримуваних кровавих спогадів.</text>
<text id="1612">Сторінка з втраченої книги рунознавця Каріла.

Каріл присвятив своє життя запису звуків,
що вимовляли Великі. Прочитайте руну Каріла,
щоб осягнути її форму.

Руна "Око" дозволяє робити більше відкриттів.</text>
<text id="1650">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most radial blood gems have effects that
bear upon physical attacks.</text>
<text id="1651">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most radial blood gems have effects that
bear upon physical attacks.</text>
<text id="1652">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most radial blood gems have effects that
bear upon physical attacks.</text>
<text id="1653">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most radial blood gems have effects that
bear upon physical attacks.</text>
<text id="1654">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most radial blood gems have effects that
bear upon physical attacks.</text>
<text id="1655">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most radial blood gems have effects that
bear upon physical attacks.</text>
<text id="1656">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a rare abyssal blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most radial abyssal blood gems have effects that bear upon physical attacks.</text>
<text id="1657">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most triangular blood gems have effects that
provide attribute bonuses and extra effects.</text>
<text id="1658">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most triangular blood gems have effects that
provide attribute bonuses and extra effects.</text>
<text id="1659">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most triangular blood gems have effects that
provide attribute bonuses and extra effects.</text>
<text id="1660">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most triangular blood gems have effects that
provide attribute bonuses and extra effects.</text>
<text id="1661">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most triangular blood gems have effects that
provide attribute bonuses and extra effects.</text>
<text id="1662">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most triangular blood gems have effects that
provide attribute bonuses and extra effects.</text>
<text id="1663">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a rare abyssal blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most triangular blood gems have effects that provide attribute bonuses and extra effects.</text>
<text id="1664">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most waning blood gems provide rare special effects
such as fire, bolt, or healing.</text>
<text id="1665">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most waning blood gems provide rare special effects
such as fire, bolt, or healing.</text>
<text id="1666">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most waning blood gems provide rare special effects
such as fire, bolt, or healing.</text>
<text id="1667">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most waning blood gems provide rare special effects
such as fire, bolt, or healing.</text>
<text id="1668">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most waning blood gems provide rare special effects
such as fire, bolt, or healing.</text>
<text id="1669">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most waning blood gems provide rare special effects
such as fire, bolt, or healing.</text>
<text id="1670">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a rare abyssal blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Most waning blood gems provide rare special effects such as fire, bolt, or healing.</text>
<text id="1671">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem which
 fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Circular blood gems are normally used to
fortify firearms.</text>
<text id="1672">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Circular blood gems are normally used to fortify firearms.</text>
<text id="1673">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Circular blood gems are normally used to fortify firearms.</text>
<text id="1674">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Circular blood gems are normally used to fortify firearms.</text>
<text id="1675">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Circular blood gems are normally used to fortify firearms.</text>
<text id="1676">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Circular blood gems are normally used to fortify firearms.</text>
<text id="1677">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a rare abyssal blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Circular abyssal blood gems are normally used to fortify firearms.</text>
<text id="1678">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Droplet blood gems are special gems that adapt
to various weapons and shapes.</text>
<text id="1679">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Droplet blood gems are special gems that adapt
to various weapons and shapes.</text>
<text id="1680">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Droplet blood gems are special gems that adapt
to various weapons and shapes.</text>
<text id="1681">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Droplet blood gems are special gems that adapt
to various weapons and shapes.</text>
<text id="1682">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Droplet blood gems are special gems that adapt
to various weapons and shapes.</text>
<text id="1683">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a blood gem
which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Droplet blood gems are special gems that adapt
to various weapons and shapes.</text>
<text id="1684">Petrified Blood Gem. Polish to gain a rare abyssal blood gem which fortifies weapons and adds various properties.

Droplet abyssal blood gems are special gems that adapt to various weapons and shapes.</text>
<text id="1700">A centipede-like creature discovered on successful hunts by League hunters.

Vermin, found hidden within filth, are only seen by League confederates, and are the root of man's impurity. The League has assumed the task of finding and crushing all vermin.

Perhaps there is some mercy in the madness. Those who wish to see vermin can, and those who choose to are provided with boundless purpose.</text>
<text id="2000">Remnant of the eldritch Truth encountered at Byrgenwerth.

Use phantasms, the invertebrates known to be augurs of the Great Ones, to partially summon abandoned Ebrietas.

The initial encounter marked the start of an inquiry into the cosmos from within the old labyrinth, and led to the establishment of the Choir.</text>
<text id="2001">%null%</text>
<text id="2002">%null%</text>
<text id="2003">%null%</text>
<text id="2004">%null%</text>
<text id="2005">%null%</text>
<text id="2006">%null%</text>
<text id="2007">%null%</text>
<text id="2008">%null%</text>
<text id="2009">%null%</text>
<text id="2010">One of the secret rites of the Choir.

Long ago, the Healing Church used phantasms to reach
a lofty plane of darkness, but failed to make contact
with the outer reaches of the cosmos.

The rite failed to achieve its intended purpose,
but instead created a small exploding star, now
a powerful part of the Choir's arsenal. At times,
failure is the mother of invention.</text>
<text id="2011">%null%</text>
<text id="2012">%null%</text>
<text id="2013">%null%</text>
<text id="2014">%null%</text>
<text id="2015">%null%</text>
<text id="2016">%null%</text>
<text id="2017">%null%</text>
<text id="2018">%null%</text>
<text id="2019">%null%</text>
<text id="2020">One of the forbidden hunter tools made by Irreverent Izzy.

Borrow the strength of the terrible undead darkbeasts, if only for a moment, to blast surrounding foes back with the force of a roaring beast.

The indescribable sound is broadcast with the caster's own vocal cords, which begs the question, what terrible things lurk deep within the frames of men?</text>
<text id="2021">%null%</text>
<text id="2022">%null%</text>
<text id="2023">%null%</text>
<text id="2024">%null%</text>
<text id="2025">%null%</text>
<text id="2026">%null%</text>
<text id="2027">%null%</text>
<text id="2028">%null%</text>
<text id="2029">%null%</text>
<text id="2030">A heavy, syrupy liquid medicine.

Temporarily shifts weight to make deflection
of attacks easier, but must be used with care,
as it also slows movement with no change to defense.

Its recipe for this mysterious concoction is unknown,
but some postulate that it materializes only within
the most desperate nightmares.</text>
<text id="2050">Special hunter tool of the Choir, high-ranking
members of the church. Fashioned after a bell that
projects an arcane sound across planes of existence.

The sound of this smaller, silver version of the bell
does not cross planes, but grants vigor and healing
to all cooperators.</text>
<text id="2051">%null%</text>
<text id="2052">%null%</text>
<text id="2053">%null%</text>
<text id="2054">%null%</text>
<text id="2055">%null%</text>
<text id="2056">%null%</text>
<text id="2057">%null%</text>
<text id="2058">%null%</text>
<text id="2059">%null%</text>
<text id="2060">The bone of an old hunter whose name is lost.

It is said that he was an apprentice to old Gehrman,
and a practitioner of the art of Quickening,
a technique particular to the first hunters.

It is most appropriate that hunters, carriers of
the torch who are sustained by the dream,
would tease an old art from his remains.</text>
<text id="2061">%null%</text>
<text id="2062">%null%</text>
<text id="2063">%null%</text>
<text id="2064">%null%</text>
<text id="2065">%null%</text>
<text id="2066">%null%</text>
<text id="2067">%null%</text>
<text id="2068">%null%</text>
<text id="2069">%null%</text>
<text id="2070">Tonitrus is a unique weapon crafted by Archibald,
the infamous eccentric of the Healing Church workshop.

This is a similar morning star mace that utilizes
Quicksilver Bullets. When struck into the ground,
it recreates the blue sparks that are said to surround
the darkbeasts.

Like Archibald's masterpiece, this too
is a superb conductor of the powerful blue sparks.</text>
<text id="2071">%null%</text>
<text id="2072">%null%</text>
<text id="2073">%null%</text>
<text id="2074">%null%</text>
<text id="2075">%null%</text>
<text id="2076">%null%</text>
<text id="2077">%null%</text>
<text id="2078">%null%</text>
<text id="2079">%null%</text>
<text id="2080">One of the secret treasures hidden in Cainhurst.
The gloves of an executioner from a faraway land.

Passed from executioner father to executioner son,
these gloves can be used to summon wrathful spirits
of the past by smearing them with blood.

It is said that the nobles found immeasurable delight
in the dances of these vengeful specters.</text>
<text id="2081">%null%</text>
<text id="2082">%null%</text>
<text id="2083">%null%</text>
<text id="2084">%null%</text>
<text id="2085">%null%</text>
<text id="2086">%null%</text>
<text id="2087">%null%</text>
<text id="2088">%null%</text>
<text id="2089">%null%</text>
<text id="2090">A blade of bone coated with gruesome spinal fluid.
Used by old labyrinth Watchers, in particular, those presiding over rituals.

When a victim is cut by this blade, the green spinal fluid temporarily numbs the senses, disturbing the target's gross motor skills. The blade, never intended for battle, must cut deep to be effective, and breaks.</text>
<text id="2110">A strange gift from the messengers, inhabitants of
the dream who revere the brave hunters.

Use to envelop oneself in a black nightmarish mist,
then transform into a messenger. The illusion is a parlor
trick, and any large movement will break the spell.

To preserve the guise, proceed very slowly.</text>
<text id="2111">%null%</text>
<text id="2112">%null%</text>
<text id="2113">%null%</text>
<text id="2114">%null%</text>
<text id="2115">%null%</text>
<text id="2116">%null%</text>
<text id="2117">%null%</text>
<text id="2118">%null%</text>
<text id="2119">%null%</text>
<text id="2120">Soft eye blessed by a phantasm.
They were discovered through Byrgenwerth's contact with the arcane, but in the end revealed nothing.

Deep within the eye lies a vast stretch of dark sky that rumbles with an endless meteor storm.
The slightest rub of the tiny orb, and the rock will tumble and soar.</text>
<text id="2121">%null%</text>
<text id="2122">%null%</text>
<text id="2123">%null%</text>
<text id="2124">%null%</text>
<text id="2125">%null%</text>
<text id="2126">%null%</text>
<text id="2127">%null%</text>
<text id="2128">%null%</text>
<text id="2129">%null%</text>
<text id="2130">Skull of a local from the violated fishing village. The inside of the skull was forcibly searched for eyes, as evidenced by innumerable scratches and indentations.

No wonder the skull became stewed in curses.

They who offer baneful chants.
Weep with them, as one in trance.</text>
<text id="2131">%null%</text>
<text id="2132">%null%</text>
<text id="2133">%null%</text>
<text id="2134">%null%</text>
<text id="2135">%null%</text>
<text id="2136">%null%</text>
<text id="2137">%null%</text>
<text id="2138">%null%</text>
<text id="2139">%null%</text>
<text id="2140">Whistle of the Madaras twins, denizens of the Forbidden Woods.
The twins grew up alongside a poisonous snake, and developed a silent, inhuman kinship.

The poisonous snake grew uncontrollably, raised on a healthy diet of beast entrails. Even after their deaths, it is said to respond to the call of the twins' whistle from within the Nightmare.</text>
<text id="3000">A solid shard that forms in coldblood.

After death, a substance in the blood hardens, and that which does not crystalize is called a blood stone.

At the workshop, these bloodstones are embedded in weapons to fortify them.</text>
<text id="3001">%null%</text>
<text id="3002">%null%</text>
<text id="3003">%null%</text>
<text id="3004">%null%</text>
<text id="3005">%null%</text>
<text id="3006">%null%</text>
<text id="3007">%null%</text>
<text id="3008">%null%</text>
<text id="3009">%null%</text>
<text id="3010">A solid shard that forms in coldblood.

After death, a substance in the blood hardens, and that which does not crystalize is called a blood stone.

At the workshop, these bloodstones are embedded in weapons to fortify them.</text>
<text id="3011">%null%</text>
<text id="3012">%null%</text>
<text id="3013">%null%</text>
<text id="3014">%null%</text>
<text id="3015">%null%</text>
<text id="3016">%null%</text>
<text id="3017">%null%</text>
<text id="3018">%null%</text>
<text id="3019">%null%</text>
<text id="3020">A solid chunk that forms in coldblood.

After death, a substance in the blood hardens, and that which does not crystalize is called a blood stone.

A chunk will never appear in the blood of an ordinary human. Seek deadlier foes if bloodstone chunks are needed.</text>
<text id="3021">%null%</text>
<text id="3022">%null%</text>
<text id="3023">%null%</text>
<text id="3024">%null%</text>
<text id="3025">%null%</text>
<text id="3026">%null%</text>
<text id="3027">%null%</text>
<text id="3028">%null%</text>
<text id="3029">%null%</text>
<text id="3030">A large solid chunk that forms in coldblood.

After death, a substance in the blood hardens, and that which does not crystalize is called a blood stone.

This is no mere chunk, it is nearly a boulder.

Few blood stones of such size have ever been discovered, even considering the combined experience of all the hunters.</text>
<text id="4000">Key to the gate that blocks the Tomb of Oedon.

Beyond the tomb, Oedon Chapel can be found
in the center of the Cathedral Ward.

Only today the church is abandoned, and some
say that the residents of Oedon have all gone mad.</text>
<text id="4001">Pendant of Vicar Amelia. Use to change into
a blood gem, which fortifies weapons.

This pendant, passed down among the vicars who
head the Healing Church, is a reminder of the cautionary
adage, words that will open the gates of Byrgenwerth.</text>
<text id="4002">*</text>
<text id="4003">An old blood-stained summons, inviting an honored
guest to the forsaken Castle Cainhurst.

Rather bafflingly, it is addressed to you.

Do not hesitate; the stagecoach leaves from
Hemwick crossing.</text>
<text id="4004">*</text>
<text id="4005">*</text>
<text id="4006">Key to the Orphanage, birthplace of the Choir.

The Orphanage, shadowed by the Grand Cathedral,
was a place of scholarship and experimentation,
where young orphans became potent unseen thinkers
for the Healing Church.

The Choir, that would later split the Healing Church,
was a creation of the Orphanage.</text>
<text id="4007">*</text>
<text id="4008">*</text>
<text id="4009">Of the three great bridges that link the two
cathedral cradles, this key opens the iron door
that leads to the midlevel bridge.

There are no thieves in the nightmare. Then,
why lock a door? Be warned, there must be a very,
very good reason.</text>
<text id="4010">The key to the Upper Cathedral Ward seal.

The upper echelons of the Healing Church are formed
by the School of Mensis, based in the Unseen Village,
and the Choir occupying the Upper Cathedral Ward.

This key brings one a step closer to the Choir.</text>
<text id="4011">A cloth emblem that belonged to the captain of the
Church hunters long ago. Opens the main gate that
leads to the round plaza of the Great Cathedral.

The main gate is shut tight on nights of the hunt,
and could only be opened from the other side with
this emblem. In other words, the captain's return,
and this emblem, determined the end of the hunt.</text>
<text id="4012">Key to the Lecture Theatre in the Lecture Building.

Today, the two-story Lecture Building is adrift in the nightmare, but once it was a place of reflection, where scholars learned of history and archaeology.

Perhaps it still is, as the students in the lecture theatre appear to await the return of their professor.</text>
<text id="4013">Key to the lunarium facing the lake on the second floor of Byrgenwerth College.

In his final years, Master Willem was fond of the lookout, and the rocking chair that he kept there for meditation.

In the end, it is said, he left his secret with the lake.</text>
<text id="4014">Skull of Laurence, first vicar of the Healing Church.
In reality he became the first cleric beast, and his human skull only exists within the Nightmare.

The skull is a symbol of Laurence's past, and what he failed to protect. He is destined to seek his skull, but even if he found it, it could never restore his memories.</text>
<text id="4015">Key to the inner chamber of the cell below the Grand Cathedral.

The innermost chamber of the underground cell holds a lone madman. He wears a beast hide, and rings a bell that emits no sound.

Unending death awaits those who can hear the soundless bell.</text>
<text id="4016">%null%</text>
<text id="4017">An eye pendant which unlocks the surgery altar.

There are two cathedrals in the Hunter's Dream. One lies past the River of Blood, and another contains the private research hall of the Healing Church.

Only chosen members of the Healing Church, or their lamentable patients, can enter the research hall, using this eye.

Grant eyes to the surgery altar skull.</text>
<text id="4018">Key to the cell below the Grand Cathedral.

Hunters are held within the underground cell, so that things better left unseen, and knowledge better left unknown, will decay quietly in the fallow darkness.</text>
<text id="4019">Key to the balcony on the first floor of the Research Hall.

Lady Maria of the Astral Clocktower gave this to the patient, Adeline.
Maria had hoped Adeline would find comfort in the faint breeze that carried the scent of flowers from the outside, but Adeline couldn't fathom her intentions.</text>
<text id="4020">Key to the Astral Clocktower at the top of the Grand Cathedral.

The caretaker of the tower's numerous patients, known to them only as Lady Maria, made her home behind the giant star-interpreting clock.</text>
<text id="4021">A celestial dial that functions with the giant Astral Clock in the Grand Cathedral.

When the dial is held up toward the Astral Clock, the clock will come to life, and reveal a secret to its curious interloper.</text>
<text id="4102">A misplaced workshop tool from the Hunter's Dream.

The hunter who retrieves this can extract Arcane Haze
from ritual materials.

But alas, spent materials are lost.</text>
<text id="4103">A misplaced workshop tool from the Hunter's Dream.

The hunter who retrieves this can fortify weapons by
kneading blood gems into them.

Blood gems add properties to weapons when used to
fortify them, as blood defines an organism.</text>
<text id="4104">Runesmith Caryll, student of Byrgenwerth,
transcribed the inhuman utterings of the Great Ones
into what are now called Caryll Runes.

The hunter who retrieves this workshop tool can etch
Caryll Runes into the mind to attain their wondrous
strength.

Provost Willem would have been proud of Caryll's runes,
as they do not rely upon blood in any measure. </text>
<text id="4105">One of the root chalices that breaks various seals in the Old Labyrinth.

The glass chalice, when full, is used in a short ritual to quickly create and join a Chalice Dungeon (not for use in a ritual using standard materials).

Short rituals are conducted at the makeshift altar.</text>
<text id="4106">%null%</text>
<text id="4107">%null%</text>
<text id="4108">%null%</text>
<text id="4109">%null%</text>
<text id="4110">Badge crafted long ago at the Workshop.
Attests to one's prowess as a hunter of beasts.

The Workshop is gone, and no group recognizes
this meaningless badge, except the messengers
in the bath, who understand its profundity.

Certain things can only be entrusted with a hunter
in possession of this badge, or so they believe.</text>
<text id="4111">Badge of a Hunter of Hunters, who hunts those who have become addled with blood.

The badge of the Hunter of Hunters is quietly passed down from generation to generation, usually to an outsider from the hinterlands.

To be entrusted with this cursed badge, one must be strong, resilient to the seduction of blood, and gracious when taking a comrade's life.</text>
<text id="4112">Badge crafted by the Powder Kegs,
the heretics of the Workshop.

The Powder Kegs adoration of complex design and
big booms culminated in weapon designs that
contrast with those traditionally of the Workshop.

The late Powder Kegs, bless their souls, had a motto:
"If a weapon ain't got kick, it just ain't worth it."</text>
<text id="4113">This hunter's badge, crafted in Gehrman's time,
has no practical purpose, except perhaps to
assist in romanticizing about the past.

The badge was a special privilege for the hunters
of the past, and should not be dishonored.

It should be left in peace, unless one is truly
prepared to assume the will of those gone before.</text>
<text id="4114">One of the badges crafted by the Healing Church.
The silver sword is a symbol of a Church hunter.

Ludwig was the first of many Healing Church hunters
to come, many of whom were clerics. As it was,
clerics transformed into the most hideous beasts.</text>
<text id="4115">One of the badges crafted by the Healing Church.

The radiant sword indicates the heirs to the will of Ludwig.

These hunters, also known as Holy Blades, are what remains of an ancient line of heroes that date back to a very early age of honor and chivalry.</text>
<text id="4116">Martyr Logarius led a band of Executioners, and this badge was crafted at their dedicated workshop. The wheel symbolizes righteous destiny.

Their workshop was a secretive enclave of mystical beliefs and heady fanaticism which served as the backbone of the Executioners' unique brand of justice.</text>
<text id="4117">Badge of the royal guards of Cainhurst, loyal guardians of the Vileblood Queen Annalise.

The Vilebloods are hunters of blood, and hunt prey as they search for blood dregs. The hunter who joins them is faced with a decision: to merely borrow their strength, or to become one of them, heart and soul.</text>
<text id="4118">Badge crafted in secret by Archibald, the infamous eccentric of the Healing Church, for his friends.

Archibald was fascinated by the blue sparks that emanate from the hides of the darkbeasts, and dedicated his life to its artificial reproduction, in a style of inquiry that, incidentally, closely followed the methodology of Byrgenwerth.</text>
<text id="4119">Badge of a member of the Choir, elites of the
Healing Church.

The eye signifies the very cosmos.

The Choir stumbled upon an epiphany, very suddenly
and quite by accident. Here we stand, feet planted in
the earth, but might the cosmos be very near us, only
just above our heads?</text>
<text id="4120">Badge crafted by the Oto Workshop, precursor to the workshop of the heretical Powder Kegs.

The Powder Kegs were driven by singular ideas, and crafted strange weapons of great intricacy.
It is clear that the philosophy of the Powder Kegs was already established at this time.</text>
<text id="4121">%null%</text>
<text id="4200">*</text>
<text id="4300">A small, very ordinary hair ornament.

Although it has been lost for quite some time,
one can still see signs of the care with which
this tasteful ornament was once kept.

Its color would stand out most brilliantly against
a head of grayish hair.</text>
<text id="4301">Silver-shining tear stone.

Use to change into a droplet blood gem
that fortifies any weapon.

A doll sheds neither blood nor tears, and thus its
nature remains unknown. Whoever thinks this is
precious must be troubled by severe naiveté.</text>
<text id="4302">%null%</text>
<text id="4303">*</text>
<text id="4304">The inhuman beings known as the Great Ones imbued this ring of betrothal with some special meaning.

In the age of the Great Ones, wedlock was a blood contract, only permitted to those slated to bear a special child.</text>
<text id="4305">What remains of Annalise, blood queen of Cainhurst.

This pinkish lump of flesh remains warm, as if cursed.
All hail the undying queen of blood!</text>
<text id="4306">A woman's bright-red brooch, engraved with the name Viola.

Perhaps the jewel is a gift from a hunter. Use to change into a droplet blood gem that fortifies any weapon.

With the proper workshop tool, various weapons can be fortified.</text>
<text id="4307">*</text>
<text id="4308">An old, sealed summons.

Like the first of its kind, it is an invitation to Cainhurst, but for whom is not known, as it lacks an addressee.</text>
<text id="4309">*</text>
<text id="4310">A latticed, deformed rock, or perhaps a meteorite.

Appears useless, but possesses some odd gravitational force that prevents its riddance. A dubious soul once said:

"Step lightly round to the right of the great cathedral, and seek an ancient, shrouded church... The gift of the godhead will grant you strength..."</text>
<text id="4311">The eye of a blood-drunk hunter. Its pupil is collapsed and turned to mush, indicating the onset of the scourge of beasts.

A hunter who goes drunk with blood is said to be taken by the Nightmare, destined to wander forever, engaged in an endless hunt. It is a fate that no hunter can escape.</text>
<text id="4312">One of the resonating bells that cross the gaps of worlds.
This bell is cracked and stained with the blood of beasts.

A human must expend Insight to ring this uncanny bell.

The old hunters, who have long passed from the dream but cannot forget the feeling of the hunt, rely upon messengers to relay their thoughts.
Ring the bell at their side, and they are certain to give a listen.
For the night of the hunt is long, and unchanging.</text>
<text id="4313">%null%</text>
<text id="4314">%null%</text>
<text id="4315">%null%</text>
<text id="4316">%null%</text>
<text id="4317">%null%</text>
<text id="4318">%null%</text>
<text id="4319">%null%</text>
<text id="4320">A great relic, also known as the Cord of the Eye. Every infant Great One has this precursor to the umbilical cord.

Every Great One loses its child, and then yearns for a surrogate. The Third Umbilical Cord precipitated the encounter with the pale moon, which beckoned the hunters and conceived the Hunter's Dream.

Use to gain Insight and, so they say, eyes on the inside, although no one remembers what that truly entails.</text>
<text id="4321">A great relic, also known as the Cord of the Eye. Every infant Great One has this precursor to the umbilical cord.

Every Great One loses its child, and then yearns for a surrogate, and Oedon, the formless Great One, is no different. To think, it was corrupted blood that began this eldritch liaison.

Use to gain Insight and, so they say, eyes on the inside, although no one remembers what that truly entails.</text>
<text id="4322">A great relic, also known as the Cord of the Eye. Every infant Great One has this precursor to the umbilical cord.

Provost Willem sought the Cord in order to elevate his being and thoughts to those of a Great One, by lining his brain with eyes. The only choice, he knew, if man were to ever match Their greatness.</text>
<text id="4323">A great relic, also known as the Cord of the Eye. Every infant Great One has this precursor to the umbilical cord.

Every Great One loses its child, and then yearns for a surrogate. This Cord granted Mensis audience with Mergo, but resulted in the stillbirth of their brains.

Use to gain Insight and, so they say, eyes on the inside, although no one remembers what that truly entails.</text>
<text id="4324">%null%</text>
<text id="4325">%null%</text>
<text id="4326">%null%</text>
<text id="4327">%null%</text>
<text id="4328">%null%</text>
<text id="4329">%null%</text>
<text id="4330">A sacred heirloom left by Yharnam, Pthumerian Queen.

The Queen lies dead, but her horrific consciousness
is only asleep, and stirs in unsettling motions.</text>
<text id="4331">%null%</text>
<text id="4332">%null%</text>
<text id="4333">%null%</text>
<text id="4334">%null%</text>
<text id="4335">%null%</text>
<text id="4336">%null%</text>
<text id="4337">%null%</text>
<text id="4338">%null%</text>
<text id="4339">%null%</text>
<text id="4340">Greyish amoeba-shaped brain fluid. Wobbles and bounces.

Extracted from a patient whose head expanded until that was all that they were.

Once, a young girl had an older brother who was determined to become a doctor, and so she willfully became his patient. In the end, this led to their encounter with the Eldritch Truth, for which they considered themselves blessed.</text>
<text id="4341">Greyish amoeba-shaped brain fluid. Wobbles and bounces.

Extracted from a patient whose head expanded until that was all that they were.

In the early days of the Healing Church, the Great Ones were linked to the ocean, and so the cerebral patients would imbibe water, and listen for the howl of the sea.
Brain fluid writhed inside the head, the initial makings of internal eyes.</text>
<text id="4342">Greyish amoeba-shaped brain fluid. Wobbles and bounces.

Extracted from a patient whose head expanded until that was all that they were.

We fail to realize our own latent potential, until the moment it is lost, and we sense its absence. Ironically, this is the very nature of insight, like the moment one licks one's own blood, only to be startled by its sweetness.</text>
<text id="4900">Hat that messengers are oddly fond of.
Commonly called a Yharnam hat.

The inhabitants of the stump appear to
have an interest in adornment. Why not
let them be happy, and revel as babes?</text>
<text id="4901">A worn, rumpled top hat that messengers are oddly fond of.

The inhabitants of the stump appear to have an interest in adornment. Why not let them be happy, and revel as babes?</text>
<text id="4902">Accessory adored by naïve messengers imitating the
bandages of scourge victims, unaware of their meaning.

The inhabitants of the stump appear to have an
interest in adornment. Why not let them be happy,
and revel as babes?</text>
<text id="4903">White ribbon that messengers are oddly fond of.

A ribbon made of fine lace that shines remarkably,
more suited to pretty young girls than
silly old messengers.</text>
<text id="4904">Red ribbon that messengers are oddly fond of.

The thick, pungent red was drawn from the organs
of some unfortunate victim.

A strange choice indeed, but perhaps for the messengers
wearing this accessory constitutes a form of mourning.</text>
<text id="4905">Hat that messengers are oddly fond of.
A nice top hat rounds out any Yharnam gentleman.

The inhabitants of the stump appear to have an
interest in adornment. Why not let them be happy,
and revel as babes?</text>
<text id="4906">Hat that messengers are oddly fond of.
Symbol of the preventative hunters of
the Healing Church.

The inhabitants of the stump appear to have an
interest in adornment. Why not let them be happy,
and revel as babes?</text>
<text id="4907">Accessory adored by naïve messengers imitating the
bandages of scourge victims, unaware of their meaning.
The spatters of blood give it a particularly nice touch.

The inhabitants of the stump appear to have an
interest in adornment. Why not let them be happy,
and revel as babes?</text>
<text id="4908">Accessory adored by naïve messengers.
The messengers wear the urns, filled with incense
that wards off beasts, on their heads upside-down,
suggesting a predilection to the dark.

The inhabitants of the stump appear to have an
interest in adornment. Why not let them be happy,
and revel as babes?</text>
<text id="6100">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

The old labyrinth was carved out by the Pthumerians,
superhuman beings that are said to have unlocked
the wisdom of the eldritch Truth.</text>
<text id="6101">*</text>
<text id="6102">%null%</text>
<text id="6103">%null%</text>
<text id="6104">%null%</text>
<text id="6105">%null%</text>
<text id="6106">%null%</text>
<text id="6107">%null%</text>
<text id="6108">%null%</text>
<text id="6109">Ritual chalice found in the Church of the Good Chalice.

Use in a ritual at the tomb altar in the Hunter's Dream
to break the seal of the old underground labyrinth.

Let the chalice reveal the tomb of the gods; let blood
be the hunter's nourishment.

...And let ye partake in communion...</text>
<text id="6200">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

The old labyrinth was carved out by the Pthumerians,
superhuman beings that are said to have unlocked
the wisdom of the eldritch Truth.</text>
<text id="6201">%null%</text>
<text id="6202">%null%</text>
<text id="6203">%null%</text>
<text id="6204">%null%</text>
<text id="6205">%null%</text>
<text id="6206">%null%</text>
<text id="6207">%null%</text>
<text id="6208">%null%</text>
<text id="6209">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.

But only a Root Chalice changes the shape of the
old labyrinth when used in a ritual.

The old labyrinth was carved out by the Pthumerians,
superhuman beings that are said to have unlocked
the wisdom of the eldritch Truth.</text>
<text id="6210">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

The hintertombs are unceremonious homes to graves
and death, cesspools of noxious snakes and insects.</text>
<text id="6211">%null%</text>
<text id="6212">%null%</text>
<text id="6213">%null%</text>
<text id="6214">%null%</text>
<text id="6215">%null%</text>
<text id="6216">%null%</text>
<text id="6217">%null%</text>
<text id="6218">%null%</text>
<text id="6219">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.
Hintertombs are the peripheral catacombs
of the old underground labyrinth.

To this day, the Watchers continue to expand the
hintertombs, unceremonious catacombs filled with
graves and death.</text>
<text id="6300">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

The old labyrinth was carved out by the Pthumerians,
superhuman beings that are said to have unlocked
the wisdom of the eldritch Truth.</text>
<text id="6301">%null%</text>
<text id="6302">Root chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

When used in a ritual, this sinister chalice summons the Sinister Resonant Bell. The bell-ringing woman appears to be a mad Pthumerian.
The old labyrinth was carved out by the Pthumerians, superhuman beings that are said to have unlocked the wisdom of the eldritch Truth.

Note: Additional rite Sinister Bell is for online use only.
The bell-ringing woman does not appear offline.</text>
<text id="6303">%null%</text>
<text id="6304">%null%</text>
<text id="6305">%null%</text>
<text id="6306">%null%</text>
<text id="6307">%null%</text>
<text id="6308">%null%</text>
<text id="6309">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.

But only a Root Chalice changes the shape of the
old labyrinth when used in a ritual.

The old labyrinth was carved out by the Pthumerians,
superhuman beings that are said to have unlocked
the wisdom of the eldritch Truth.</text>
<text id="6310">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

The hintertombs are unceremonious homes to graves
and death, cesspools of noxious snakes and insects.</text>
<text id="6311">%null%</text>
<text id="6312">Root chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.
When used in a ritual, this sinister chalice summons the Sinister Resonant Bell. The bell-ringing woman appears to be a mad Pthumerian.

The hintertombs are unceremonious homes to graves and death, cesspools of noxious snakes and insects.

Note: Additional rite Sinister Bell is for online use only.
The bell-ringing woman does not appear offline.</text>
<text id="6313">%null%</text>
<text id="6314">%null%</text>
<text id="6315">%null%</text>
<text id="6316">%null%</text>
<text id="6317">%null%</text>
<text id="6318">%null%</text>
<text id="6319">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.
Hintertombs are the peripheral catacombs
of the old underground labyrinth.

To this day, the Watchers continue to expand the
hintertombs, unceremonious catacombs filled with
graves and death.</text>
<text id="6401">Root chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

This cursed chalice makes a special ritual possible, but must not be used lightly, as the resulting transformation can be utterly drastic.

The old labyrinth was carved out by the Pthumerians, superhuman beings that are said to have unlocked the wisdom of the eldritch Truth.</text>
<text id="6402">%null%</text>
<text id="6403">%null%</text>
<text id="6404">%null%</text>
<text id="6405">%null%</text>
<text id="6406">%null%</text>
<text id="6407">%null%</text>
<text id="6408">%null%</text>
<text id="6409">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.

Only, this defiled chalice is cursed.

Curses are caused by inciting the anger of the Great Ones, and used to hex others. Special materials are required to complete the ritual.

To try one's hand at curses, first seek the Bastard of Loran.</text>
<text id="6420">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

There are trace remains of medical procedures in
parts of ailing Loran. Whether these were attempts to
control the scourge of the beast, or the cause of the
outbreak, is unknown.</text>
<text id="6421">%null%</text>
<text id="6422">%null%</text>
<text id="6423">%null%</text>
<text id="6424">%null%</text>
<text id="6425">%null%</text>
<text id="6426">%null%</text>
<text id="6427">%null%</text>
<text id="6428">%null%</text>
<text id="6429">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.
Loran is a tragic land that was devoured by the sands.

The tragedy that struck this ailing land of Loran
is said to have its roots in the scourge of the beast.

Some have made the dreaded extrapolation that
Yharnam may be next.</text>
<text id="6500">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

The Pthumerian monarch was traditionally a woman
who assumed a name with classical roots.</text>
<text id="6501">%null%</text>
<text id="6502">Root chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.
When used in a ritual, this sinister chalice summons
the Sinister Resonant Bell. The bell-ringing woman
appears to be a mad Pthumerian.

The Pthumerian monarch was traditionally a woman
who assumed a name with classical roots.

Note: Additional rite Sinister Bell is for online use only.
The bell-ringing woman does not appear offline.</text>
<text id="6503">%null%</text>
<text id="6504">%null%</text>
<text id="6505">%null%</text>
<text id="6506">%null%</text>
<text id="6507">%null%</text>
<text id="6508">%null%</text>
<text id="6509">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.

Great chalices unlock deeper reaches of the labyrinth.
Pthumeru Ihyll was the title of both the
Pthumerian monarch and its capital.

This reveals that while early Pthumerians were mere
humble guardians of the slumbering Great Ones, their
descendants felt entitled to name themselves a leader.</text>
<text id="6520">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

There are trace remains of medical procedures in
parts of ailing Loran. Whether these were attempts to
control the scourge of the beast, or the cause of the
outbreak, is unknown.</text>
<text id="6521">%null%</text>
<text id="6522">Root chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

When used in a ritual, this sinister chalice summons the Sinister Resonant Bell. The bell-ringing woman appears to be a mad Pthumerian.
There are trace remains of medical procedures in parts of ailing Loran. Whether these were attempts to control the scourge of the beast, or the cause of the
outbreak, is unknown.
Note: Additional rite Sinister Bell is for online use only.
The bell-ringing woman does not appear offline.</text>
<text id="6523">%null%</text>
<text id="6524">%null%</text>
<text id="6525">%null%</text>
<text id="6526">%null%</text>
<text id="6527">%null%</text>
<text id="6528">%null%</text>
<text id="6529">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.
But only a Root Chalice changes the shape of the
Chalice Dungeon when used in a ritual.

There are trace remains of medical procedures in
parts of ailing Loran. Whether these were attempts to
control the scourge of the beast, or the cause of the
outbreak, is unknown.</text>
<text id="6530">Root Chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

Root Chalices, used in rituals to break old labyrinth
seals, are said to change the labyrinth's form each time.

According to the Choir, the land of Isz lies in contact
with the cosmos, which allowed the Great Ones to
function on transcendental planes of thought.</text>
<text id="6531">%null%</text>
<text id="6532">Root chalice that breaks multiple labyrinth seals.

When used in a ritual, this sinister chalice summons the Sinister Resonant Bell. The bell-ringing woman appears to be a mad Pthumerian.
According to the Choir, the land of Isz lies in contact with the cosmos, which allowed the Great Ones to function on transcendental planes of thought.

Note: Additional rite Sinister Bell is for online use only.
The bell-ringing woman does not appear offline.</text>
<text id="6533">%null%</text>
<text id="6534">%null%</text>
<text id="6535">%null%</text>
<text id="6536">%null%</text>
<text id="6537">%null%</text>
<text id="6538">%null%</text>
<text id="6539">A chalice that breaks a labyrinth seal.

Great chalices unlock deeper reaches of the labyrinth.
The Great Isz Chalice became the cornerstone of the
Choir, the elite delegation of the Healing Church.

It was also the first Great Chalice brought back to the
surface since the time of Byrgenwerth, and allowed
the Choir to have audience with Ebrietas.</text>
<text id="7000">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

One of the basic ingredients used to satiate a Holy Chalice is this incoagulable blood.

When all is melted in blood, all is reborn.</text>
<text id="7001">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

One of the basic ingredients used to satiate a Holy Chalice is this incoagulable blood.

When all is melted in blood, all is reborn.</text>
<text id="7002">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

One of the basic ingredients used to satiate a Holy Chalice is this incoagulable blood.

When all is melted in blood, all is reborn.</text>
<text id="7003">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

One of the basic ingredients used to satiate a Holy Chalice is this incoagulable blood.

When all is melted in blood, all is reborn.</text>
<text id="7004">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

One of the basic ingredients used to satiate a Holy Chalice is this incoagulable blood.

When all is melted in blood, all is reborn.</text>
<text id="7005">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

The remains of a skull used in a ceremony.

A vestige of the bizarre rites carried out by the
old labyrinth Watchers.</text>
<text id="7006">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

A perfect specimen, surrounded by a faint flame.

A vestige of the bizarre rites carried out by the
old labyrinth Watchers.</text>
<text id="7007">*</text>
<text id="7008">*</text>
<text id="7009">%null%</text>
<text id="7010">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Pale vegetation that commonly grows on coldblood inside the old labyrinth.</text>
<text id="7011">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Pale vegetation that commonly grows on coldblood inside the old labyrinth.</text>
<text id="7012">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Pale vegetation that commonly grows on coldblood in a place long ago abandoned.</text>
<text id="7013">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Pale vegetation that commonly grows on coldblood in a place long abandoned, said to mature slowly in close proximity to death, and eventually bloom.</text>
<text id="7014">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Pale vegetation that commonly grows on coldblood in a place long abandoned, that has bloomed into a bright red stygian flower. </text>
<text id="7015">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Pale bulb that commonly grows on coldblood inside the old labyrinth, said to mature slowly in the abyss, and eventually bloom.</text>
<text id="7016">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Pale vegetation that commonly grows on coldblood inside the old labyrinth that has bloomed into a bright red stygian flower. </text>
<text id="7017">*</text>
<text id="7018">*</text>
<text id="7019">%null%</text>
<text id="7020">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Mold that grows from rotten flesh and blood inside the old labyrinth. Matures to bear giant spores.</text>
<text id="7021">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Mold that grows from rotten flesh and blood inside the old labyrinth. Matures to bear giant spores.</text>
<text id="7022">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Mold that grows from rotten flesh and blood inside the old labyrinth. Matures to bear giant spores.</text>
<text id="7023">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Mold that grows from rotten flesh and blood inside the old labyrinth. Matures to bear giant spores.</text>
<text id="7024">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Mold that grows from rotten flesh and blood inside the old labyrinth. Matures to bear giant spores.</text>
<text id="7025">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Mold that grows from rotten flesh and blood inside the old labyrinth. Matures to bear giant spores.</text>
<text id="7026">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Mold that grows from rotten flesh and blood inside the old labyrinth. Its giant spores eventually break off and float into the air, the best moment to use the mold as a material.</text>
<text id="7027">*</text>
<text id="7028">*</text>
<text id="7050">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

The tiny smatterings of haze that are found in certain ritual materials. Sometimes required for special rites.

The additional rite Sinister Bell makes the bell-ringing woman appear, and when she rings a sinister bell, hunters from other worlds will be beckoned as adversaries.</text>
<text id="7100">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Of the all the strange lifeforms that reside in the nooks and crannies of the old labyrinth, the slugs are clear signs of the left-behind Great Ones.</text>
<text id="7101">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

One of the basic ingredients used to satiate a Holy
Chalice is this incoagulable blood.

When all is melted in blood, all is reborn.</text>
<text id="7102">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

One of the basic ingredients used to satiate a Holy
Chalice is this incoagulable blood.

When all is melted in blood, all is reborn.</text>
<text id="7103">*</text>
<text id="7104">*</text>
<text id="7105">*</text>
<text id="7106">*</text>
<text id="7107">*</text>
<text id="7108">*</text>
<text id="7109">%null%</text>
<text id="7110">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Stillborn infants born of a creature of unknown origin, of the type found in some corners of the old labyrinth.</text>
<text id="7111">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Strange creatures lurk in the nooks and crannies of the
old labyrinth.</text>
<text id="7112">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Strange creatures lurk in the nooks and crannies of the
old labyrinth.</text>
<text id="7113">%null%</text>
<text id="7114">%null%</text>
<text id="7115">%null%</text>
<text id="7116">%null%</text>
<text id="7117">%null%</text>
<text id="7118">%null%</text>
<text id="7119">%null%</text>
<text id="7120">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

A body part of a saint, sacrificed by the Healing Church in their search for Truth.

The additional rite Fetid Offering invigorates the Watchers, making them more treacherous than normal, but also making them worthy prey for a special hunt.</text>
<text id="7121">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

A body part of a saint, sacrificed by the Healing Church in their search for Truth.

The additional rite Fetid Offering invigorates the Watchers, making them more treacherous than normal, but also making them worthy prey for a special hunt.</text>
<text id="7122">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

A body part of a saint, sacrificed by the Healing Church in their search for Truth.

The Church's experiments with blood have successfully produced specimens perfect for sacrifice.</text>
<text id="7123">%null%</text>
<text id="7124">%null%</text>
<text id="7125">%null%</text>
<text id="7126">%null%</text>
<text id="7127">%null%</text>
<text id="7128">%null%</text>
<text id="7129">%null%</text>
<text id="7130">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Special body parts collected by the Healing Church.
What was this gruesome bait used to lure?

The additional rite Rotted Offering beckons ungodly forces, normally terrifying things, but also worthy prey for a special hunt.</text>
<text id="7131">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Special body parts collected by the Healing Church.
What was this gruesome bait used to lure?

The additional rite Rotted Offering beckons ungodly forces, normally terrifying things, but also worthy prey for a special hunt.</text>
<text id="7132">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Special body parts collected by the Healing Church.

Corpse-ridden Yharnam was the perfect place for the collection of specimens such as these.</text>
<text id="7133">%null%</text>
<text id="7134">%null%</text>
<text id="7135">%null%</text>
<text id="7136">%null%</text>
<text id="7137">%null%</text>
<text id="7138">%null%</text>
<text id="7139">%null%</text>
<text id="7140">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

Remains of Loran infant infected by the scourge.
A harbinger of curses and symbol of defilement.

The additional rite Curse defiles dungeons in which hunters' HP is greatly eroded, but what better place to seek cursed blood gems but in the midst of defilement?</text>
<text id="7141">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

A stillborn infant born of a creature of unknown origin, of the type found in some corners of the old labyrinth.

The apprentices of Byrgenwerth were fascinated by newborns, perhaps due to the stunning quality of these remains.</text>
<text id="7142">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

A stillborn infant born of a creature of unknown origin, of the type found in some corners of the old labyrinth.

The apprentices of Byrgenwerth were fascinated by newborns, perhaps due to the stunning quality of these remains.</text>
<text id="7143">%null%</text>
<text id="7144">%null%</text>
<text id="7145">%null%</text>
<text id="7146">%null%</text>
<text id="7147">%null%</text>
<text id="7148">%null%</text>
<text id="7149">%null%</text>
<text id="7150">Material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

An exquisite eyeball removed quickly after death, or perhaps even before. Used to unlock the seal of the old labyrinth hintertombs.</text>
<text id="7200">Special material used in a Holy Chalice ritual.

The immense brain that Mensis retrieved from the nightmare was indeed lined with eyes on the inside, but they were of an evil sort, and the brain itself was terribly rotten.

But even still, it was a legitimate Great One, and left a relic. A living relic, at that, which is a precious thing indeed.</text>
<text id="10900">*</text>
<text id="10901">%null%</text>
<text id="10902">%null%</text>
<text id="10903">%null%</text>
<text id="10904">%null%</text>
<text id="10905">%null%</text>
<text id="10906">%null%</text>
<text id="10907">%null%</text>
<text id="10908">%null%</text>
<text id="10909">%null%</text>
<text id="10910">*</text>
<text id="11000">*</text>
<text id="11100">*</text>
<text id="11101">*</text>
<text id="11102">%null%</text>
<text id="11103">%null%</text>
<text id="11104">%null%</text>
<text id="11105">%null%</text>
<text id="11106">%null%</text>
<text id="11107">%null%</text>
<text id="11108">%null%</text>
<text id="11109">%null%</text>
<text id="11110">*</text>
<text id="11111">%null%</text>
<text id="11112">%null%</text>
<text id="11113">%null%</text>
<text id="11114">%null%</text>
<text id="11115">%null%</text>
<text id="11116">%null%</text>
<text id="11117">%null%</text>
<text id="11118">%null%</text>
<text id="11119">%null%</text>
<text id="11120">*</text>
<text id="11121">%null%</text>
<text id="11122">%null%</text>
<text id="11123">%null%</text>
<text id="11124">%null%</text>
<text id="11125">%null%</text>
<text id="11126">%null%</text>
<text id="11127">%null%</text>
<text id="11128">%null%</text>
<text id="11129">%null%</text>
<text id="11130">*</text>
<text id="11200">*</text>
<text id="11201">%null%</text>
<text id="11202">%null%</text>
<text id="11203">%null%</text>
<text id="11204">%null%</text>
<text id="11205">%null%</text>
<text id="11206">%null%</text>
<text id="11207">%null%</text>
<text id="11208">%null%</text>
<text id="11209">%null%</text>
<text id="11210">*</text>
<text id="11211">%null%</text>
<text id="11212">%null%</text>
<text id="11213">%null%</text>
<text id="11214">%null%</text>
<text id="11215">%null%</text>
<text id="11216">%null%</text>
<text id="11217">%null%</text>
<text id="11218">%null%</text>
<text id="11219">%null%</text>
<text id="11220">*</text>
<text id="11221">%null%</text>
<text id="11222">%null%</text>
<text id="11223">%null%</text>
<text id="11224">%null%</text>
<text id="11225">%null%</text>
<text id="11226">%null%</text>
<text id="11227">%null%</text>
<text id="11228">%null%</text>
<text id="11229">%null%</text>
<text id="11230">*</text>
<text id="11231">%null%</text>
<text id="11232">%null%</text>
<text id="11233">%null%</text>
<text id="11234">%null%</text>
<text id="11235">%null%</text>
<text id="11236">%null%</text>
<text id="11237">%null%</text>
<text id="11238">%null%</text>
<text id="11239">%null%</text>
<text id="11240">*</text>
<text id="11241">%null%</text>
<text id="11242">%null%</text>
<text id="11243">%null%</text>
<text id="11244">%null%</text>
<text id="11245">%null%</text>
<text id="11246">%null%</text>
<text id="11247">%null%</text>
<text id="11248">%null%</text>
<text id="11249">%null%</text>
<text id="11250">*</text>
<text id="11251">%null%</text>
<text id="11252">%null%</text>
<text id="11253">%null%</text>
<text id="11254">%null%</text>
<text id="11255">%null%</text>
<text id="11256">%null%</text>
<text id="11257">%null%</text>
<text id="11258">%null%</text>
<text id="11259">%null%</text>
<text id="11260">*</text>
<text id="11261">%null%</text>
<text id="11262">%null%</text>
<text id="11263">%null%</text>
<text id="11264">%null%</text>
<text id="11265">%null%</text>
<text id="11266">%null%</text>
<text id="11267">%null%</text>
<text id="11268">%null%</text>
<text id="11269">%null%</text>
<text id="11270">*</text>
<text id="11300">*</text>
<text id="11301">%null%</text>
<text id="11302">%null%</text>
<text id="11303">%null%</text>
<text id="11304">%null%</text>
<text id="11305">%null%</text>
<text id="11306">%null%</text>
<text id="11307">%null%</text>
<text id="11308">%null%</text>
<text id="11309">%null%</text>
<text id="11310">*</text>
<text id="11311">%null%</text>
<text id="11312">%null%</text>
<text id="11313">%null%</text>
<text id="11314">%null%</text>
<text id="11315">%null%</text>
<text id="11316">%null%</text>
<text id="11317">%null%</text>
<text id="11318">%null%</text>
<text id="11319">%null%</text>
<text id="11320">*</text>
<text id="11321">%null%</text>
<text id="11322">%null%</text>
<text id="11323">%null%</text>
<text id="11324">%null%</text>
<text id="11325">%null%</text>
<text id="11326">%null%</text>
<text id="11327">%null%</text>
<text id="11328">%null%</text>
<text id="11329">%null%</text>
<text id="11330">*</text>
<text id="12000">*</text>
<text id="12001">%null%</text>
<text id="12002">%null%</text>
<text id="12003">%null%</text>
<text id="12004">%null%</text>
<text id="12005">%null%</text>
<text id="12006">%null%</text>
<text id="12007">%null%</text>
<text id="12008">%null%</text>
<text id="12009">%null%</text>
<text id="12010">*</text>
<text id="12011">%null%</text>
<text id="12012">%null%</text>
<text id="12013">%null%</text>
<text id="12014">%null%</text>
<text id="12015">%null%</text>
<text id="12016">%null%</text>
<text id="12017">%null%</text>
<text id="12018">%null%</text>
<text id="12019">%null%</text>
<text id="12020">*</text>
<text id="12021">%null%</text>
<text id="12022">%null%</text>
<text id="12023">%null%</text>
<text id="12024">%null%</text>
<text id="12025">%null%</text>
<text id="12026">%null%</text>
<text id="12027">%null%</text>
<text id="12028">%null%</text>
<text id="12029">%null%</text>
<text id="12030">*</text>
<text id="12050">*</text>
<text id="12051">%null%</text>
<text id="12052">%null%</text>
<text id="12053">%null%</text>
<text id="12054">%null%</text>
<text id="12055">%null%</text>
<text id="12056">%null%</text>
<text id="12057">%null%</text>
<text id="12058">%null%</text>
<text id="12059">%null%</text>
<text id="12060">*</text>
<text id="12061">%null%</text>
<text id="12062">%null%</text>
<text id="12063">%null%</text>
<text id="12064">%null%</text>
<text id="12065">%null%</text>
<text id="12066">%null%</text>
<text id="12067">%null%</text>
<text id="12068">%null%</text>
<text id="12069">%null%</text>
<text id="12070">*</text>
<text id="12071">%null%</text>
<text id="12072">%null%</text>
<text id="12073">%null%</text>
<text id="12074">%null%</text>
<text id="12075">%null%</text>
<text id="12076">%null%</text>
<text id="12077">%null%</text>
<text id="12078">%null%</text>
<text id="12079">%null%</text>
<text id="12080">*</text>
<text id="12081">%null%</text>
<text id="12082">%null%</text>
<text id="12083">%null%</text>
<text id="12084">%null%</text>
<text id="12085">%null%</text>
<text id="12086">%null%</text>
<text id="12087">%null%</text>
<text id="12088">%null%</text>
<text id="12089">%null%</text>
<text id="12090">*</text>
<text id="12110">*</text>
</entries>
</fmg>
